pinkvisual.com 2017-11-19

# Pink Visual- Milf Porn, Erotica, Mobile and Tech XXX

PinkVisual.com is firmly committed to respecting and maintaining the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy explains our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by visitors to PinkVisual.com. By using this site, you signify your assent to our privacy practices and the terms and conditions of PinkVisual.com. If this policy is not agreeable to you, please do not use PinkVisual.com.

## What type of information is collected?

We only collect personal information from visitors to and customers of PinkVisual.com that is voluntarily supplied to us by completing our signup form, or by way of electing to use one or more of the services provided on PinkVisual.com. We may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, birth date, username, password, and on occasion, some other manner of unique identifier.

## In what way do we use your personal and non-personal information?

When visitors access PinkVisual.com, certain non-personal information may be collected from them including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Firefox), operating system (e.g., Windows, iOS), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site (e.g., google.com). In addition, we may collect information about visitors’ browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the PinkVisual.com, the areas or pages of our PinkVisual.com that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing PinkVisual.com, the number of times the visitor returns to PinkVisual.com, and click-stream data.

We use proprietary javascript as well as third-party scripts like Google Analytics to determine the number of PinkVisual.com visitors that have been sent to us through our affiliate network. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave PinkVisual.com. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on visitors’ computers when they access our Web site) to collect this information. Information collected through cookies may be combined with visitors' personal information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Web site. Visitors are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Web site. The “help” segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when it receives a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from your hard drive(s).

We may use information collected from visitors to our Web site for any of the following purposes: (1) to send visitors information and promotional materials about our company, (2) to send visitors information and promotional materials from our marketing partners and third parties (such as advertisers on our Web site), (3) to deliver targeted display advertisements by matching criteria provided by our advertisers with information collected from our visitors, (4) to contact visitors to our Web site when necessary, (5) to allow convenient, easily affected purchases or access to proprietary content by pre-populating fields, within registration or other transaction screens, with a visitor's name, billing address, and email (among other things), as provided by that visitor, (6) to help diagnose problems with our server, (7) to administer our Web site, (8) to conduct internal reviews of our site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the site), (9) to help us better understand visitors' use of our site, and (10) to protect the security or integrity of our site. Non-personal information will be used for purposes of conducting internal reviews of the site, monitoring the site, and providing a greater online experience for our visitors.

## What security measures do we take to protect your information?

To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data integrity, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from visitors to PinkVisual.com. We allow access to personal information only to persons and entities engaging in activities provided for by this Privacy Policy. Visitors should consider any communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or communications submitted to a chat room) to be non-confidential. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to a visitor is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

## Corporate changes.

In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset or stock sale, bankruptcy, or other asset transfer (regardless of legal formality), any of our assets may be transferred to a third party, including personal information collected from visitors to our Web site.

## Acceptance of privacy terms & conditions

By visiting PinkVisual.com, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting PinkVisual.com, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of PinkVisual.com. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Web site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. PinkVisual.com is not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies.

## Changes to this privacy policy

There may be times when we need to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices, please bookmark this page and check back often.

## How can you access the information we have collected from you?

Visitors who wish to access or change the information they provided to PinkVisual.com, should visit the Contact Us page of PinkVisual.com, select “Customer Service” from the subject dropdown menu, and use the contact form to contact our customer service department via Email.

Previous PageBack to top
